<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello! I am Kartik Gulati</title>
    <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello! I am Kartik Gulati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Kartik Gulati&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:55:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> The Voyager | Travel and E-Com</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/voyager/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/voyager/</guid>
      <description>The primary functionality of the VOYAGER is the combination of eCommerce and informational blog websites. There are three main end-users, and every user has their perspective. The first one is Admin, which has all the administrative functionalities related to the customer&amp;rsquo;s order manipulation, a list of all the logged-in users and Blog management.
Whereas Logged users have the authority to purchase the travel package published by the Admin and can draft their own travel experiences in the form of the Blog for other travellers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Instruments | Business website</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/paramount/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/paramount/</guid>
      <description>Paramount Instruments Pvt. Ltd. is an associate company of the well- known “Paramount Group” , an ISO 9001 : 2015, ISO 14001 : 2015, ISO 45001:2018 Certified Group, Established in 1964. At Paramount, we are committed to providing OUTSTANDING QUALITY CONTROL SOLUTIONS and WORLD CLASS Testing Instruments for Textiles, Yarn, Fabric Inspection, Footwear, Leather, Artificial Leather, Automotive, Coated Fabrics, Non-Woven, Paper, Cardboard &amp;amp; Packaging Industry.
Technology used to develop the Website: Wordpress,PHP 8,CSS 3,HTML 5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anlitiqs | Company&#39;s Business Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/anlitiqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 21:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/anlitiqs/</guid>
      <description>Anlitiqs is a Digital Marketing and Web Designing Company based in Delhi, India. We provide focused, results-oriented Digital Marketing services including Web Design, Search Engine Optimization, Website Hosting, Social Media Marketing, Content Writing, Email Marketing and Mobile Marketing. We are not just a Digital Marketing company, we are your Digital Marketing partners in India. Anlitiqs expert in converting visitors into customers and increasing sales quickly. We focus on ROI and use a variety of channels to create a large reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hairkart Salon | Customer Appointment Solution</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/hairkart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 21:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/hairkart/</guid>
      <description>Hairkart Salon is based on the Customer Appointment Solution. Basically it is a system which helps businesses manage and schedule customer appointments. It typically includes features such as automated appointment reminders, online booking, customer profiles, and appointment analytics. Technology used to develop the Website: Wordpress,PHP 8,CSS 3, HTML 5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malgre Safety Shoes | E-commerce</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/malgre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 21:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/malgre/</guid>
      <description>Malgre Safety Shoes is an e-commerce website for safety shoes, This is the online store where people can shop for, compare, and purchase safety shoes. Malgre Safety Shoes include features such as product reviews, detailed product descriptions, and filtering options to allow customers to easily find the perfect pair of safety shoes for their needs. Payment processing options is also be available so customers can quickly pay for their purchases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$Contact</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 21:31:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/contact/</guid>
      <description>I would be available on Twitter almost all time except my sleep xD. Best would be ping me there for anything. If you don’t have Telegram, no problemo, you can reach me out on Instagram.
For any formal correspondence, Email which has become too formal: [kartikgulati19@gmail.com](mailto: kartikgulati19@gmail.com)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$whoami</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 20:59:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Kartik Gulati, a young Web Developer, Blogger and a Tech lover(geek), popularly known around the internet world as Kartik Gulati. If you ﬁnd some­one with the user­name Welcome2GulatiCityon any platform, you can be mostly sure its me.
If you still want to know more about me then download my Resume .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechOutputs | Tech Blogging Website</title>
      <link>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/techoutputs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kartikgulati.github.io/itskg/projects/techoutputs/</guid>
      <description>TechOutputs is a technological blogging website, which provides daily tech updates, technological news, and a plethora of new inventions related to the tech world. Here you can also find the reviews of smartphones, smart tablets, laptops, and computer systems and hardware. I post regular content on TechOutputs, so that you are always updated about what is going on in Tech.
Here is the link of TechOutputs. Go and check out the latest news of Tech World</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
